Hi, Master.
Hello.
Hello, Kakwa.
How are you?
Master now needs a habit of this way.
Habit? Ah, yeah, yeah.
Hi, how are you?
Hello, Master.
Of course, Master is 30 years old.
Very nice to meet you.
老生日就在報告嘛。
報告?
So now, the celebration.
我們是要讓他們安靜的。
會是很高的。
阿姨姊姊。
姊姊。
阿彌陀佛。
這個,蔡會長。
是那個普濟會嗎?
布瓦會。
He's the leader of all volunteers here.
普濟會在這裡。
普濟會長。
He's a charitable organization here.
Charitable, yes.
And she's the director.
陳執行長。
哪個部分的執行長?
布瓦會。
布瓦會的。
He's the main official.
All devotees here.
All the devotees here.
I think you met him.
And he also visited your campus.
Long time ago.
我說你很久很久以前
跟那個住持法師。
Now it is time to visit again.
This long time ago.
有機會應該要再去的,很久了。
司團長。
司工團的團長。
He's also a very important member.